客厅  晚上九点零三分
Living room, 9:03 p.m.
电磁场侦测器接收到前所未有的强烈信号
EMF level spiking off the chart.
有人吗
Hello?
有人在那吗
Is anyone there?
梅夕[仁慈]
Mercy...
我看见了
I can see it.
梅夕[仁慈]
Mercy...
不
No!
老爸  你在用我做肉盾
Dad, are you using me as a shield
挡在食人僵尸前面吗
against flesh-eating zombies?
不  不是  我只是想让你有个好点的视野
No. No. I just wanted you to have a better view.
你去哪  我认为
Where are you going? I think--
我真的认为我们还是一起看安全点
I really think we're safer in pairs.
抱歉  老爸  你得自己保护自己了
Sorry, dad. You're gonna have to fend for yourself.
我要去和阿什利视频了
I'm skyping with ashley.
什么
What?
就这么打断我们的父女赏僵尸时间
Right in the middle of father-daughter zombie time?
迟点再聊行不行
Can't you do it later?
他待会就没空了
He's not available later.
他要参加宿舍会议和研讨班
He's got a dorm meeting and then a seminar after that.
我知道他是个忙人
I know he's busy,
你的随和也非常贴心  宝贝
and you are very thoughtful to be so accommodating, sweetheart,
但健康的关系建立在互相尊重的基础上
but a healthy relationship is based on mutual respect.
你总是为他改变原本的行程安排
I mean, think about what kind of signal you're sending
对他有求必应  你想想
if you're the one always rearranging your schedule
如此行为向他发出了怎样的信号
at the other one's every beck and call.
只要他一叫你
I mean, if you just drop everything...
你就抛下手边的事...抱歉
the very moment that-- I'm sorry.
等等
Oh, hang on.
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
马上到
I'll be right there.
我很担心阿丽克西斯
I'm worried about Alexis.
我认为没能考入斯坦福影响了
I think her not getting into Stanford
她在与阿什利的关系中的地位
has upset the balance of power in her relationship with Ashley.
卡塞尔  换了是我就不会担心
Oh, Castle, I wouldn't worry about that.
阿丽克西斯是女孩  阿什利是个少年
I mean, Alexis is a girl, and Ashley's a teenage boy.
我认为她还是占有主导地位的
I'd say she still holds most of the power.
"牧鬼人"摄制组在这
The "Ghost Wranglers" are here?
这就是我迷他们的原因
Okay, that's why I love these guys.
尸骨未寒
Body's not even cold,
他们就已经开始追踪鬼魂了
they're already tracking down the ghost.
你爱看那荒唐的节目怎么
Why doesn't it surprise me that you actually watch
一点也没让我觉得惊讶
that ridiculous show?
荒唐地好看
Ridiculously awesome.
杰克·辛克莱毫无疑问
Jack Sinclair is hands down
是全美最出色的猎鬼人
America's most accomplished ghost hunter.
卡塞尔
Um, Castle...
杰克·辛克莱就是死者的名字
Jack Sinclair is the name of our victim.
猎人反被猎杀
And the hunter becomes the hunted.
他在这录制一个关于屋子的特辑
He was here doing a special about the house,
就是为他的节目
you know, for his TV show.
为什么选这里
Why this place?
这地方有点历史
It has a bit of a history.
你是指超自然的历史
You mean, paranormal history?
探长  我不是说我自己
Look, detective, I'm not saying
相信这些东西  好吗
I believe in that stuff, okay?
但我拥有麦拉伦老宅超过二十年了
But I've owned the McClaren House for over 20 years,
当这个地方出问题的时候
and when the phone rings about this place,
基本不会是马桶坏了
odds are, it's not a busted toilet.
现在有人住在这里吗
Anybody live in there now?
很久没人住了
Not for years.
租客总是住不长
It's hard getting tenants to stick around.
所以当辛克莱联系我的时候
So when this Sinclair guy called,
我想管它呢
I figured, what the hell?
也许他能除妖降魔啥的
Maybe he could clear the place up,
就能再出租了
make it rentable.
但鉴于刚刚发生的事...
But after what just happened...
刚刚到底发生了什么事
Wh-what exactly did just happen?
他的喉部被切开  差不多切至两耳根
His throat was slit almost from ear to ear.
颈静脉  甲状腺动脉
Jugular, superior thyroid,
左右颈动脉
common carotid, left and right--
能断的都切断了
You name it, it's been severed.
那就解释了大量的血迹
Well, that explains all the blood.
这一点  我无法解释
Here's what I can't explain--
伤口的深度及性质表明
Depth and nature of the wounds tell me
凶手与死者的距离一定很近
that the killer got up close and personal.
那他的脚印在哪
So then where are the footprints?
不止这些  瞧这些血迹的溅落
Not just that. Look at the blood spatter.
切断这么些动脉
You cut all those arteries,
血液应该会立刻
and the spray is gonna come fast
并且强烈地喷出来
and it's gonna come strong.
我说那一定喷得满世界都是
I'll say. It went everywhere.
但不该如此
But it shouldn't have.
部分血迹本该溅到凶手身上
Some of it should've landed on the killer.
但每一滴血都落在了地上
Yet every drop of it landed on the floor.
溅落完全没有遇到任何阻碍物
This spray is completely unobstructed.
正是
Exactly.
这根本说不通
It doesn't make sense.
除非血滴穿透了凶手的身体
Unless the blood passed right through the killer.
你是说凶手是鬼吗
Are you saying a ghost did this?
别鼓励他胡扯了
Please don't encourage him.
我是说
I'm saying,
也许辛克莱先生终于碰到
maybe Mr. Sinclair finally met a wraith
他收不了的恶灵了
he couldn't wrangle.
蕾妮  报案的是什么人
Lanie, who called this in?
我是杰克的制片人
I'm... Jack's producer.
已经和他一起工作四年了
I worked with him for the last four years.
好的露露  我们只是想了解一下
Okay, Lulu, we just need to know
在你报警之前发生的所有事
everything that happened before you called 911.
好的
Okay.
杰克在七点左右进入这屋子
Jack went in the house at around 7:00.
几分钟后就把自己禁闭了
And then he went on lockdown a few minutes after that.
把自己关在一间屋子里过夜
Uh, he locks himself into the house for the night.
是猎鬼人的标准方案
It's standard protocol for ghost hunters.
-就他一个人在里面吗  -是的
- And was he in there alone? - Yeah.
在开始之前  我们总是会
We always do a clean sweep of the place
进行一次清查
right before we start.
然后他...  他把门锁上
So he--he locked the doors,
我就上技术器材装载车看监控了
and then I went into the tech van to watch the feed.
这段时间  摄影机一直在拍摄吗
And were the cameras rolling the whole time?
红外摄影机是用来监测
The infrared cameras are to detect
无法解释的热量异常
unexplained thermal anomalies.
客厅  晚上九点零三分
Living room, 9:03 p.m..
电磁场侦测器接收到前所未有的强烈信号
EMF level spiking off the chart.
那是针对电磁场运动的侦测器
That's an electromagnetic field meter.
捉鬼这行必备的行头
That's a tool of the ghost busting trade.
用来侦测超自然力量的信号
It's used to measure spikes in paranormal energy.
认真看吧
Let's just watch.
有人吗
Hello?
有人在那吗
Is anyone there?
梅夕[仁慈]
Mercy...
我看见了
I can see it.
梅夕[仁慈]
Mercy...
他好像在求凶手发慈悲  手下留情
It sounds like he was begging his killer for mercy.
发生什么事了
What happened?
没了  就这么多
That--that's it.
所有摄影机在那一刻全都被中断了
That's when all the camera signals cut out at once.
所有画面都没了
And what could explain the picture
是什么造成的呢
suddenly going out like that?
我不知道  以前从没发生过
I don't know. It's never happened before.
《黑道家族》最后一集就是这样
Well, there was that last episode of "The Sopranos."
不  没可能的
No, there's no way.
当时一定有人跟杰克在一起
Jack had to have been in there with someone else.
他有任何敌人吗
Did he have any enemies,
最近跟他有矛盾的人
anybody that he was having problems with recently?
没有  至少我不知道
No, not that I know of.
他来禁闭时的确有点心烦意乱的
He... he did show up to lockdown upset.
-你知道他是从哪过来的吗  -不知道
- Do you know where he was coming from? - No.
他从计程车上下来  拿了他的工具
He pulled up in a cab and grabbed his gear
就进去了
and just went inside.
还有人有此处的钥匙吗
Did anyone else have keys to this place?
只有杰克和巴里·B
Just Jack and Barry B.
巴里·巴夫塔  杰克的摄影师
Barry Bavetta. That's Jack's cameraman.
巴里人呢
Where is Barry?
他通常不是与杰克一起禁闭吗
Doesn't he usually do lockdown with Jack?
今天下午他和杰克吵了一架
He and Jack had an argument this afternoon.
闹得很僵  然后巴里就辞职了
Things got pretty heated, and then Barry just quit.
他有可能把摄影机设置成
Could he have programmed the cameras
像那样自动关闭吗
to turn off like that?
事实上  他是可以的
Actually... Yeah, he could.
巴里·巴夫塔于七点半急忙地从酒店退房
Barry Bavetta checked out of his hotel in a hurry at 7:30.
足够他在九点杰克被杀的时候
That's enough time to make it back to the house
回到宅子里
by 9:00 when Jack was killed.
巴里的电话还是直转语音信箱
Barry's phone is still going straight to voice mail.
经理把他的信用卡信息给我了
Well, the manager gave me his credit card info,
如果走运  他可能会用卡
so if we're lucky he's out there using it.
好吧  我得开始啃那卷
All right, I'm gonna start scrubbing this footage
在屋里拍的录影带了
from inside of the house.
也许里面有些什么会涉及到这家伙
Maybe there's something in there that can implicate this guy.
好的  嘿
Right. Hey.
我们明天还是一起吃晚餐  对吧
We're still on for dinner tomorrow night, right?
对  珍妮兴奋极了
Oh, yeah. Jenny's totally psyched.
她从来都没和蕾妮一起出去过  这不错
She's never really hung out with Lanie before, so cool.
提前告诉你一声
Well, just to let you know,
那会儿蕾妮刚下双班
Lanie's gonna be getting off a double shift,
她会有点暴躁的
so she could be a little cranky.
那我们还是改日子吧
Oh. Maybe we should reschedule.
我是说这不都是为了
I mean, isn't the whole point
让蕾妮和和珍妮好好相处吗
for Jenny and Lanie to get along?
没事  她会很亲切的
Nah, she'll be cool.
只是别提什么有争议性的话题
Just, you know, don't say anything controversial.
比如说
Like what?
什么叫有争议性的
What's controversial?
宾果[既有答对了的意思也是游戏名]
Bingo.
宾果  不能说宾果游戏
Bingo? Don't talk about bingo?
巴里·巴夫塔一直挺忙  他的大腿也没闲着
Barry Bavetta's been busy, and so has his lap.
这哥们在机场边上的脱衣舞俱乐部挥霍了一大笔钱
Dude has racked up a hell of a tab at a strip club by the airport.
第一次消费  谋杀案发后一小时
First charge, an hour after the murder.
抱歉打断了你的乐子  巴里
Sorry to interrupt your fun, Barry.
我们听说你花了一大笔钱
We heard you were racking up quite a bill.
用来买"波涛汹涌"了
Or is that billing quite a rack?
那怎么了  看大腿舞也违法了
So what, getting a lap dance is illegal now?
听着  我就是想找点乐子
Look, I was just blowing off some steam.
一天都不太顺
Haven't had the best day.
是啊  我们也听说了
Yeah, so we heard.
你的制片人说你和杰克·辛克莱
Your producer said that you and Jack Sinclair
今天吵架了
had a falling out today.
那这是和杰克有关了  是
So this is about Jack? Yeah.
我们是吵起来了
We got into it.
这也不是我们第一次争吵了
Wasn't the first fight we ever had,
但是我保证是最后一次了
but I made sure it'll be the last.
你何不说说怎么回事呢  巴里
Why don't you tell us what happened, Barry?
就是杰克耍了我这么回事
Jack screwed me over is what happened.
他最后时刻告诉我
He told me last-minute
我今晚不能和他一起进入到禁区里了
I wasn't going with him on lockdown tonight.
为什么
Any reason?
他给我的唯一原因就是他是老板
The only one he gave was, he's the boss.
但实际上是他妒忌我
But... It's 'cause he's jealous.
担心我会抢走他的风头
Worried I'm gonna walk off with all the credit.
为什么
Why is that?
因为我们今晚拍摄的这一集
Because the episode we're doing tonight,
麦拉伦老宅  是我的主意
the McClaren House, was my idea.
我做了所有的调查
I did all the research.
杰克根本就不想拍
Jack didn't even want to do the damn show.
他为什么不想拍
Why wouldn't Jack want to do
一个纽约的鬼屋凶宅呢
a show about a haunted mansion in New York?
听起来收视保证登顶啊
That sounds like ratings gold.
杰克对纽约很别扭
Jack's weird about New York.
他在这里长大
He was brought up here,
但是他却对回到这里有些古怪的厌恶
but he's got some strange aversion to coming back.
他试图阻拦整件事
He tried to torpedo the whole thing,
说他才不会在那间房子里出洋相[死]呢
said he wouldn't be caught dead in that house.
所以你就决定证明他是错的
And you decided to prove him wrong?
什么
What?
杰克·辛克莱今晚在麦拉伦老宅被杀
Jack Sinclair was killed in the McClaren House tonight.
被杀了
Killed?
巴里  你为什么不把钥匙还给房主呢
Barry, why didn't you give your keys back to the owner?
因为  我
Uh, I'm--I was--
我太生气了  我忘了
I was, uh, upset. I forgot.
他真的死了
Is--is--is he really dead?
你是设置机位的人  对吗
You were the one who set up the cameras, right?
是
Yeah.
所以呢
So?
所以你知道摄像机的确切位置
So you knew exactly where they were placed
也知道当你潜回宅子时如何才能不被拍到
and how to avoid them when you snuck back in the house.
你甚至知道如何设定它们
You even knew how to program them
让它们在特定的时间关闭
to turn off at a certain point.
打住  打住  我才没杀杰克
Whoa, whoa. I did not kill Jack.
我根本就不在场
I wasn't even there.
我被安检拖住了
I got stuck in the security line
错过了去洛杉矶的飞机
and missed my flight to L.A.
之后我就直接去了脱衣舞俱乐部
I went to the strip club right after that.
你们可以查到的
You can check that.
运输安全局证实了巴里
So T.S.A. has Barry
在九点一刻通过肯尼迪机场安检
going through security at 9:15 at J.F.K.
他根本不可能在案发时
There's no way that he was in the house
出现在案发现场
at the time of the murder.
另外技术人员检查了那些摄像机
Plus, tech checked out those cameras.
它们的关闭并不是设定好的
They weren't programmed to turn off.
巴里只是消磨[杀掉]了
The only thing Barry's guilty of killing
在脱衣舞俱乐部的欢乐时光
is time at that strip club.
所以  如果巴里不是我们要找的人
So... If Barry's not our guy,
那我想我们应该再考虑有没有可能
I think it's time we revisit the possibility
我们的凶手是个
that our killer's a--
你要说是鬼  我就赶你回家
If you say ghost, I'm sending you home.
美国幽灵
Apparition-American.
你找出了解释血迹的其他原因了吗
Have you figured out another way to explain the blood spatter?
目前还没  但是会的
No, I haven't, but I will.
杰克·辛克莱今晚
Apparently Jack Sinclair was very upset
坐计程车来的时候心烦意乱
when he arrived in a taxi cab tonight,
我们查查他的上车地点
so let's find out where that cab picked him up
和他在那里都做了些什么
and what he was doing there.
收到
Roger that.
等着瞧吧  卡塞尔  这个案子和其他的
You'll see, Castle. This will turn out just like
谋杀案调查没什么区别
every other murder investigation.
我们一旦了解更多死者生前的事
Once we find out more about our victim's life,
和他死亡的细节
the details surrounding his death,
一切事情就都能解释了
everything will be explained.
或许有的事解释不了
Maybe not everything.
我在复查今晚宅子里的录像
I was reviewing the footage shot inside the house tonight
寻找那里当时有其他人的迹象
looking for signs that someone else was there--
影子  倒影  什么的
A-a shadow, a reflection, something.
但是  我发现
Instead, I found, uh,
你们还是自己看看吧
well, you better see for yourself.
我慢放了录像
So I slowed down the video.
看背景的三脚架
Watch the tripod in the background.
那里  你看
There. You see it.
我相信一定会有个简单的解释
I'm sure there's a perfectly simple explanation
来说明所有事情
for all of that.
那就是
There is.
鬼来了[电影《鬼驱人》的名句]
They're here.
你休息过吗
Whoa. Did you get any sleep?
都没合过眼  但是绝对值得
Not a wink, but it was worth it.
在调查了麦拉伦老宅的历史后
After researching the history of the McClaren Mansion,
我想我知道了我们的死者
I think I know what happened
猎鬼人杰克·辛克莱的遭遇了
to our victim, ghost hunter Jack Sinclair.
顺便说一声  咖啡是给你的
That coffee's for you, by the way. Oh.
那一杯  那是
Oh, the--the other one. That's...
那是
That's--
我再给你  我再给你做一杯
I'll make you a-- I'll make you one.
自从麦拉伦老宅在1898年落成后
Um, since the McClaren Mansion was built in 1898,
死人的速度让
bodies have been piling up
塔伦蒂诺的电影甘拜下风了
faster than a tarantino movie.
总计八起凶案
Eight killings in all,
首先是最早的房主罗伯特·佩特洛
starting with the original owner, Robert Pettigrew,
在1903年被掐死
strangled, 1903.
一直到梅兰妮·本顿
All the way to Melanie Benton,
在1991年被砍成了碎片
hacked to pieces in 1991.
目前的房主名叫史蒂夫·福勒
The current owner, Steve Fuller,
曾想要拆掉房子
tried to have the house torn down,
但是被有关部门认定为地标建筑
but it was declared a landmark by the society for historic--
不好意思  卡塞尔
I'm sorry, Castle.
我很感谢你的工作  真的
I appreciate your work. I do.
但是这和我们的案子有什么关系
But what does this have to do with our case?
就快说到了
Just getting to that.
似乎看起来在所有的谋杀中
It seems that in almost all of these killings,
凶手都声称  准备好了没
the killer claimed that there was a--ready for this?
和一个恶鬼有关
That a demon was responsible.
恶鬼  不是吧
A demon? Really?
这可不是人家编的  白纸黑字
I'm not making this up. It's in the books.
好吧  一个恶鬼杀了杰克·辛克莱.
Fine. A demon killed Jack Sinclair.
那我们要做什么
So what's our next step?
我们是不是要监视房子
Are we gonna stake out the house,
等着恶鬼现身  再用质子枪把它杀了
wait for the demon to show up, zap him with our proton pack?
那不是正宗的  你懂不
That's not a real thing, you know,
真正的猎鬼人不使质子枪
that real ghost hunters use.
真正的猎鬼人
Real ghost hunters?
这不是有点自相矛盾吗  伙计
Isn't that a contradiction in terms, bro?
好了  有没有人能说点和案子相关的
Okay. Does anyone have anything pertinent to our case?
我能
I do.
好
Okay.
我找到了死者当晚所乘的出租车
I tracked down that cab our vic took last night.
驾驶员的行驶记录显示
The driver's trip log says
杰克在38号和9号大街拐角处上的车
that he picked up Jack on the corner of 38th and 9th.
让警员们带着杰克的照片排查那里
Have uniforms canvass the area with jack's photo.
看看他去那里干什么
Let's see what he was up to.
还有通话记录
Oh, and phone records, too.
或许能查出点什么
Maybe that'll shed some light on things.
我觉得我能提供点
I think I can shed some light
杰克不愿意来这儿录节目的原因
on why Jack didn't want to do the show here.
我和一个前几天
Talked to an old high school pal
同他共进早餐的高中同学聊了聊
that Jack had breakfast with a couple of days ago.
原来死者以前就住在
Turns out that our vic actually used to live
麦拉伦老宅附近
right near the McClaren House.
他曾经为了避免经过那房子
Said that he used to walk a couple blocks out of his way
绕开几个街区走
just to avoid walking past it.
据说那里让他毛骨悚然
Said it gave him a creeped out feeling.
听到没  我就告诉你
You see? I am telling you,
这房子有问题
there is something going on with this house.
最后住在  那个
The last people... Well, to--
最后住在那里的住户
The last people that lived there
四年前匆匆忙忙地搬走了
moved out four years ago in a hurry.
为什么
Why?
不知道  可我觉得是时候找出谜底了
I don't know, but I think it's time we found out.
你自己随便去查吧 卡塞尔
Knock yourself out, Castle.
-你不来吗  -不  我还有谋杀案要侦破
- You're not coming? - No, I've got a murder to solve.
我去
I'll go.
-她在瞪你了  -没错
- Ooh. That's a look. - Yeah.
我被她瞪多了  快走就是了
I get these a lot. Just start walking.
-走吧  -快点
- Let's go. - Faster.
我刚在楼下看到莱恩
I just saw Ryan downstairs.
没想到你会让他和卡塞尔一起去找鬼
I can't believe you let him go chasing ghosts with Castle.
没错  也许薛吉会让史酷比少惹麻烦
Yeah. Maybe Shaggy will keep Scooby out of trouble.
而且  世事难料
Besides, you never know.
没准他们能找到些有用的东西呢
Maybe they'll come up with something useful.
你想要有用的东西
Oh, you want useful?
我刚和鉴证组谈过了
Because I just spoke to C.S.U.
他们在现场找到了
They found fingerprints at the scene
一个大活人的指纹
from a real live person, so...
他叫朗·博格  住在皇后区
His name is Ron Berger. He lives in Queens.
-已经去抓他了  -有前科吗
- They're picking him up now. - Does he have a record?
有  这小混混因为持刀抢劫
Yeah. Chuckles did eight years
蹲了八年班房
for armed robbery with a knife.
也曾涉及入室抢劫  所以
He's also dabbled in B&E, which makes
闯入个上锁的房子对他来说不成问题
breaking into a locked house no problem for this guy.
他什么时候出狱的
When did he get out of prison?
五周以前
Five weeks ago.
总算有条靠谱的线索了
Ohh, finally a lead that makes sense.
还不止如此
Oh, it gets better.
朗和死者有过节
Ron has a history with our vic.
牧鬼人曾经在五点监狱拍摄过一期节目
"Ghost Wranglers" did a piece on Five Points Correctional,
朗也入镜了
and Ron was featured.
声称他牢房里有个幽灵
Claims he was sharing his cell with a spirit.
也算是监狱人满为患的一种
Well, that's prison overcrowding for you.
看起来  卡斯珀有点过分友好了
Apparently, Casper was being a little too friendly,
对朗毛手毛脚
touching Ron in all the wrong places.
被鬼性骚扰吗
Molested by a ghost. Mm-hmm.
有的人为了上电视什么都肯做啊
Wow. Some people will do anything to get on TV.
但事与愿违
Yeah, except it backfired on him.
朗成了整个监狱的笑柄
Ron became the laughingstock of the prison yard.
他气急败坏
He got all pissed off,
给节目写了一封信
and he wrote the show a letter.
"我要让杰克·辛克莱为他所做的事
"I'm gonna make Jack Sinclair bleed
血债血偿"
for what he did to me."
是我写的信
I wrote that letter, yeah.
不过也就此为止了  我没有杀他
But that was as far as it went. I-I didn't kill him.
昨晚九点你在哪里
Where were you last night at 9:00 p.m.?
我在家  看动画片
I was at home, watching cartoons.
你们可以去问我妈
You can ask my mom.
有个问题  朗  我们在麦拉伦老宅里
Well, we have a problem, Ron, because we found
发现了你的指纹
your fingerprints inside the McClaren House.
我能解释这事
I-I-I can explain that.
说吧
I'm waiting.
我不能违反我的假释规定
I-I can't violate my parole.
我不想再回去五点监狱了
I can't go back to Five Points,
不能再回牢房里  不能再和
not--not in that cell, not--not with that...
那玩意呆在一起
Thing.
你在害怕那个鬼吗
You're worried about your ghost?
朗  你现在被控凶杀
Ron, you're looking at murder.
你的不在场证明不堪一击
You've got a flimsy alibi.
整个犯罪现场布满了你的指纹
Your fingerprints are all over the crime scene.
你有作案的手法  动机  时机
You had means, motive, and opportunity.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
我的确去过那儿
I was there.
可不是昨晚
Just, uh, not last night.
是一个月以前
About a month ago.
我去是因为杰克
I was there because of Jack.
我出狱后他打电话来
He--he called me after I got out.
你威胁过杰克·辛克莱
Jack Sinclair called you,
他还给你打电话吗
after you threatened him?
他是为了监狱的节目向我道歉
To apologize for the prison show thing,
他还求我办件事
and he--he had a request.
求你什么事
What kind of a request?
是件怪事
Uh, it was a strange one.
他想让我进麦拉伦老宅拍些照
He wanted me to take pictures inside the McClaren House.
-为什么要你去  -那房子上了锁
- Why you? - It was locked up.
所以  我得闯进去
So, uh... I had to break in.
他告诉你拍照的理由了吗
Did he give you any reason for asking for those pictures?
好吧  我们需要看看那些照片
Okay. We're gonna need to see the photos.
技术部门分析了这张记忆卡
So tech analyzed the S.D. card.
日期标记没有动过手脚
Time/date stamp was not messed with.
-所以朗说的是实话了  -照片这事是真的
- So then Ron was telling the truth? - Well, about the photos.
我还是不相信那个被鬼骚扰的故事
I'm still not buying the whole "touched by a phantom" routine.
我在想杰克要这些照片的目的
I wonder what Jack wanted with all these photos.
所有的照片都是同一个房间的
You know, all of the pictures are of just one room--
客厅
The living room.
也正是犯罪现场的房间
That's the same room as the crime scene.
杰克雇了朗·博格去拍
So Jack hired Ron Berger to take pictures
他即将死在里面的房间的照片
of the very room he was gonna die in.
真让人毛骨悚然
That's creepy.
没什么毛骨悚然的  卡塞尔
That's not creepy, Castle.
我确定一切都可以被解释的
I'm sure it can all be explained
我打赌那间客厅
and I bet you that living room
和鬼怪神魔都沾不上边
has absolutely nothing to do with ghosts or demons.
那间客厅  毫无疑问
The living room, definitely.
是活动的中心点
That was the epicenter of the activity.
博伊尔女士  当你说活动时
Ms. Boyer, when you say activity...
我们一开始也不信
We didn't buy it either.
我们听说过麦拉伦老宅的各种事
We had heard all about the McClaren House,
它的历史
its history.
我们置之一笑
We laughed about it.
最开始  一切都很正常
At first, everything was fine.
接着就开始了  灯忽明忽灭
Then it started-- lights going off,
奇怪的声响  门突然关上
strange noises, doors slamming.
有什么暴力的事发生吗
Did anything violent ever happen?
有一天晚上
One night, uh,
我们听到客厅传来声响
we heard noises from the living room,
下楼去看
we went downstairs,
发现整个房间被捣毁了
found the whole room trashed.
桌子翻了过来
Tables flipped over,
书撕得四分五裂  照片打得七零八落
books ripped apart, pictures smashed.
我的天啊  这太恐怖了
Oh, my god. That's terrible.
所以你们决定搬走了吗
Is that when you decided to move out?
我们还是斗争了一番的
Not without a fight.
我们找到了那个女人  那个
We found this woman. This, um,
猎鬼人
ghost hunter.
据说她是这行里最好的
Said she was the best.
其他的猎鬼人都向她寻求帮助
Said all other ghost hunters came to her for help.
可她来看了一眼  就叫我们火速搬走
But she took one look, and told us to run like hell.
她叫什么名字
Yeah, what was her name?
梅夕
Um... Mercy.
没错  梅夕·兰格朗
That's right. Mercy Lagrande.
梅夕  我看见了  梅夕
"Mercy, I can see it. Mercy."
也许杰克·辛克莱死前
Maybe Jack Sinclair
并非在求凶手发慈悲呢
wasn't begging for mercy when he died.
他是在叫她的名字
He was saying her name.
梅夕·兰格朗
Mercy lagrande,
本名叫做梅赛德斯·金
real name, Mercedes King,
经营一家没有执照的灵异咨询所
runs an unlicensed business doing paranormal consultations.
没营业执照是有原因的
There's a reason why she's unlicensed.
看看这个犯罪记录
Check out this rap sheet.
盗用他人身份  诈骗  支票诈骗
We've got I.D. Theft, fraud, check fraud,
还有假冒神职人员
and impersonating a religious official.
看看她办公的地点  38街和第9街
Look at where her business is located--38th and 9th.
正好是死者上计程车的同一街区
That's on the same block our vic caught that cab.
所以杰克去拜访了梅夕
So Jack paid Mercy a visit,
然后心烦意乱地去了麦拉伦老宅
and then goes to the McClaren House upset.
几个小时后
Hours later,
死前还喊梅夕的名字
he says Mercy's name right before he dies.
问题在于  她和这件事有什么关联
So the question is, how is she involved in all of this?
你知道
Uh, well, you know, uh,
如果你们忙着解决谋杀案的话
Ryan and I would be glad to go check this out
莱恩和我很愿意去查这件事
if you guys are too busy solving that murder.
我已经尽我所能去帮助他了
I did what I could to help him,
可这些还不够
but I'd say it wasn't enough.
杰克·辛克莱为什么要来见你
Why did Jack Sinclair come to see you?
我曾经去过麦拉伦老宅
I've been in the McClaren House.
不管里面是什么  他要去见识一下
He was going to face whatever's in there,
于是他想听听我的意见
and he wanted my advice.
你有偿地给了他建议
Which you gave him... for a fee.
我可不是个江湖术士  探长
I'm not a charlatan, detective.
如果我是假把式  像杰克·辛克莱
Someone with Jack Sinclair's experience
这么专业的人是不会向我咨询的
wouldn't be seeking my counsel if I was.
请坐
Please.
如果他那么厉害  为什么还要你帮忙
If he was that good, why would he seek your help?
这对他来说不像其它的房子
This was not like any other house to him.
他接手这个任务的时候
When he took the assignment,
他就开始做梦
the dreams started.
开始只是些许碎片
Just glimpses at first,
房间里零零碎碎的东西
bits and pieces of a room,
可后来噩梦接踵而至
but then the dreams became nightmares--
人影  尸体
Figures, bodies.
谁的尸体
Whose bodies?
他也不知道
He didn't know.
可他说的越多
But the more we talked,
我越清楚  这些不是梦
the more it became clear to me, these weren't dreams.
那是什么
Well, what were they?
记忆
Memories.
他目睹了一场惨剧
He witnessed great evil.
这些年来一直压藏在记忆深处
Repressed it all these years.
可这些记忆太强大了
But the memories were too strong.
它们不断浮现出来
They were coming back.
那他具体记起了什么
And what was he remembering exactly?
一个女人
A woman,
血流成河  一个持刀的男人
a lot of blood, a man with a knife.
那个男人是谁
Who was the man?
他说那张脸很模糊  可逐渐清晰起来
He said the face was blurred but getting clearer.
我告诉他
I told him,
如果他回到凶案发生的房间
if he returned to the room where it happened,
或许他就能想起来
it might all come back to him.
"梅夕  我看见了"  指的是凶手的脸
"Mercy, I can see it." That's the murderer's face.
杰克在遇害前刚好恢复了记忆
Jack recovered the memory just before he was killed.
那栋房子里发生的上一起命案是在20年前
The last murder in that house was 20 years ago.
我读过案宗了
I read about the case.
没有目击者
There were no witnesses.
其实有一个
Oh, there was one.
杰克·辛克莱当时在场
Jack Sinclair was there
就在那个女人遇害当晚
the night that woman died.
他在场
He was there.
这些图片血肉模糊
The pictures aren't pretty.
梅兰妮·本顿
Melanie Benton,
1991年4月20日晚
sliced up in the McClaren house
在麦拉伦老宅被捅多刀而死
on the night of April 20, 1991.
你们猜她是在哪里被发现的
One guess where she was found.
客厅
The living room.
你真行
Give that man a prize.
那1991年  杰克·辛克莱多大  11岁吗
So 1991, Jack Sinclair is what, 11?
还住在那附近
Still living in the neighborhood.
我打赌他目睹的就是这起凶案
I'm betting this is the murder he witnessed.
是啊  可他是怎么目睹凶案
Yeah, but how did he witness a murder
却没让凶手发现呢
without the killer knowing?
我做了调查  杰克当时送报
I did some digging. Jack had a paper route,
麦拉伦老宅是其中一户
and the McClaren House was on it.
那杰克或许是去收钱的
Okay, so Jack shows up, maybe to collect money,
听到了惨叫  然后通过窗户往里偷看
hears screams, and he peers in through those windows.
那些他看到的情景  在多年后的
He started having dreams about what he'd seen
梦中出现  他想知道这梦境到底怎么回事
all those years ago, and he wanted to make sense of them.
所以死者才会雇朗·博格破门而入
And that's why our vic hired Ron Berger to break in
拍下客厅的照片
and take pictures of the living room.
凶手被逮捕了吗
Was there ever an arrest made?
没  所以说凶手还逍遥法外
No, which means the killer is still out there.
杰克·辛克莱快恢复记忆了
So Jack Sinclair is just about to recover his memory
并可能指证出凶手的身份
and possibly I.D. our killer,
紧接着就被灭口了
and he's silenced.
当时谁负责调查此案
Who was the investigating officer on the case?
我都已经退休十年了
I've been retired ten years,
还惦记着这起案子
and I still think about this one.
我第一个到达案发现场
I was the first one on the scene,
我得告诉你们  照片没能体现现场有多糟糕
and I gotta tell you, the pictures don't even do it justice,
马特·本顿对他妻子犯下的罪行让人作呕
what Matt Benton did to his poor wife.
马特·本顿  你认为梅兰妮是被
Matt Benton? You think that Melanie was killed
自己的老公所杀
by her own husband?
邻居一直在抱怨他们吵个不停
Well, the neighbors complained about constant fighting.
梅兰妮遇害当晚
We put out an A.P.B. on benton
我们就对本顿做了全面通缉
the night that Melanie was murdered,
可他溜了  潜逃至今
but he got away, and he's been on the lam ever since
很明显他就是凶手
so it doesn't take a genius to put it together.
他失踪后  你听说过他的下落吗
Did you ever hear anything about his whereabouts after he disappeared?
我们只接到过一次消息  说他在欧洲
We got one tip once about him being in Europe.
不过那是15年前的事了
But that--that's gotta be a good 15 years ago now.
有人看到他了吗
So somebody spotted him?
不  他寄了明信片给他哥哥
No, he sent postcards to his brother.
上面盖着维也纳的邮戳
They were postmarked Vienna.
上面写了什么  你还记得吗
What did they say? Do you remember?
说来说去都是一件事
They all said the same thing--
本顿声称他没有杀死他妻子
Benton claimed he wasn't responsible for his wife's death,
说什么跟恶鬼有关
something about a demon.
真的吗  他声称和恶鬼有关
Really? He claimed there was a demon involved?
是啊  还真以为有人会相信他
I know. Like anyone's gonna fall for that, right?
他以为跟他打交道的都是白痴吗
I mean, what kind of jackass did he think he was dealing with?
你追查过那些明信片的线索吗
Did you ever follow up on any of those postcards,
史密斯警探
Detective Smith?
我们找了国际刑警帮忙
We got interpol involved,
可没有确凿的证据对他不利
but without any hard evidence against the guy--
没有凶器  没有证人
No murder weapon, no witness-- you know,
我觉得他们没把这案子当回事儿
I don't think they ever took it too seriously.
那如果现在有个证人站出来呢
And what if a witness came forward now,
会有变化吗
would that change anything?
会改变一切
That would change everything.
越来越像是马特·本顿知晓了杰克的事
It sounds more and more like Matt Benton found out about Jack
决定杀人灭口
and decided to keep him quiet.
可马特是怎么发现
But how did Matt find out
杰克正在恢复记忆的
that Jack was recovering his memories?
我有个想法
I have an idea about that.
我刚在查死者的电话记录
I was rechecking our vic's phone records.
发现杰克·辛克莱死前一周
It turns out, a week before he died,
曾打电话
Jack Sinclair called
给洛哈特&威兰&本顿律师事务所
the law firm of Lockhart, Whelan and Benton.
本顿  是...
Benton? As in--
彼得·本顿  马特的哥哥
Pete Benton, Matt's brother.
马特的明信片就是寄给他的...
That's the brother that Matt was sending those postcards to and--
彼得很有可能警告马特
Pete could have easily alerted Matt
有人在问问题
that someone was asking questions,
不该问的问题
the wrong kind of questions.
我弟弟十五年前寄了那些明信片给我
My brother sent me those postcards over 15 years ago.
我都交给警察了  从那以后就没他的消息了
I gave them to the cops. I haven't heard from him since.
从那时起就没联系过吗  本顿先生
And no contact since then, Mr. Benton?
没
No.
和杰克·辛克莱聊过后也没有吗
Not even after talking to Jack Sinclair?
杰克·辛克莱是谁
Jack Sinclair?
那个猎鬼人
The ghost hunter.
他昨晚在麦拉伦老宅里被杀了
He was killed in the McClaren house last night.
我从没和杰克·辛克莱联系过
I never spoke to Jack Sinclair.
可他的电话记录却证明你们说过话
Well, his phone records show otherwise.
我每年都收到些电视制片人的电话
I get calls every year from some TV producer
打听我们家族的不幸
looking to exploit my family's tragedy
和麦拉伦老宅的传说
and the legend of the McClaren mansion.
不管这个人遭遇了什么不测  我深感遗憾
Look, it's a shame, whatever happened to this guy.
可如果他打来电话  不是我跟他通的话
But if he called here, I did not talk to him.
我当然也没和我弟弟有过联系
And I certainly haven't spoken to my brother.
那如果我们检查你的通话记录
So if we check your phone records,
查不到打到维也纳的通话记录
we won't find calls to Vienna?
我们是一家国际律师事务所
We're an international law firm.
我们的客户遍及欧洲  包括维也纳
We have clients all over Europe, including Vienna.
我们要查看你们的通话记录
We're gonna need access to those phone logs.
那你们需要搜查令
Then you need a warrant,
而你们没有足够的证据去申请
and you don't have enough to get one.
本顿先生  您的车到楼下了
Mr. Benton, your car is downstairs.
为事务所提供租车服务的是乐驾公司
The law firm's car service of choice is Execu-drive.
这些是彼得·本顿的账单明细
Here are Pete Benton's billing slips
差不多是这一个月左右的
going back a month or so.
有没有什么异常活动
Was there any unusual activity?
日常路线就是上下班这段路
Uh, daily routine's the same to and from work,
可是四天前
except for four days ago,
彼得批准车辆去肯尼迪机场接人
when Pete authorized a pickup at J.F.K.,
在国际航班候机楼
international terminal.
那或许彼得真的和弟弟有联络
Okay. So maybe Pete did have his brother on speed dial.
他们去了哪里
Where'd they go?
法威克酒店
Fairwyck Hotel.
我们把照片拿到法威克去
All right, let's take this down to the Fairwyck
看看有谁认得出马特·本顿
and see if anybody recognizes Matt Benton.
我让技术组搞了张合成的推测图
Actually, I had tech mock up an aged-up version of the photo,
20年后的马特
you know, Matt 20 years later.
等等  你们今晚不是有饭局吗
Wait a minute. Don't you guys have dinner plans tonight?
我们可以改到
Uh, we can move it to...
某个蕾妮不连班的晚上出去
some night when Lanie's not coming off a double shift.
实际上  蕾妮已经期盼很久了
Uh, actually, Lanie's really looking forward to it.
别担心  我回家顺道去一趟
You know what? No worries. It's on my way home.
确定吗
You sure?
确定我不想成为毁掉
That I don't want to be the one to blame
蕾妮美好夜晚的人吗  没错  我确定
for ruining Lanie's night out? Oh, yeah. I am sure.
说实话  理查德
Honestly, Richard,
你读一本关于百年老宅的书
how do you plan to solve a 1-day-old murder
对解决刚发生一天的凶案有什么帮助啊
by reading a book about a 100-year-old house?
你这话听起来像贝克特
You sound just like Beckett.
这些事件都恰好发生在客厅  一定是
There has to be a reason why all these things happened
有原因的
in the living room--
所有这些谋杀
All these murders, uh,
房客的家具  都在同一间房间
the tenants who had their furniture smashed,
被弄个粉碎
all in the same room.
也许是你们的恶鬼
Maybe that demon of yours
不喜欢那家具
did not like the furniture.
你找个家装师  把那装饰一新
You bring in a decorator, snazz up the place...
这些怪事也许就都打住了
All this nonsense might stop.
这话不像贝克特
Less like Beckett.
咱这不必再装饰了
No need of snazzing up here.
瞧瞧你
Look at you. Wow.
和阿什利视频  你还真的打扮一番啊
You're really taking these skype dates with Ashley seriously.
我是要去参加派对
I'm going to a party.
阿什几小时前就该打给我的
Ash was supposed to call me hours ago,
但是我等烦了
but I'm tired of waiting.
出去玩玩挺好  亲爱的
Oh, good for you, sweetheart.
玩的开心
Have a good time.
谢谢  爸爸  我午夜前会回来
Thanks, dad. I'll be back by midnight.
多谢
Thank you.
回见
Bye.
你看见她那身打扮了吗  我该担心吗
Did you see that outfit? Should I be worried?
阿什利才是该担心的人
Ashley's the one who should be worried.
相信我  如果他看见她现在出门的样子
Trust me, if he could see how she looked going out now,
他就不会那么让她干等着
he wouldn't be so quick to leave her hanging.
是不是很搞笑  阿什利打来的
Oh, isn't this funny? It's Ashley.
拒接
Decline.
就好像是他在偷听我们的对话
It's almost as if he was listening in to our conversation.
偷听
Listening in.
麦拉伦老宅的建筑师
The architect for the McClaren House,
是苏格兰人
he's from Scotland.
这很重要吗
I-Is that important?
这是关键
It's the key.
两个词
Two words--
主人的耳朵
Laird's lug.
Laird's lug?
也就是"房东的耳朵"
Literally "lord's ear."
指的是许多苏格兰城堡里
It refers to the hidden alcove above a dining hall
餐厅上方都设有密室
of many Scottish castles.
屋主用它来偷听客人的谈话
The host could use it to eavesdrop on his guests.
我想我要么是喝多了  要么还得再喝
I think I've either had too much wine or not enough.
西莫斯·麦拉伦  麦拉伦老宅的建筑师
Seamus McClaren, builder of the McClaren house,
紧挨着爱丁堡城堡长大
grew up right next to Edinburgh castle,
对主人的耳朵再熟悉不过了
notable for its laird's lug.
这个设计使他如此着迷
The concept so tickled him,
于是他将现代版的偷听密室
he put modern versions of it
放进了他设计的几座楼房中
into several of his houses.
你是说麦拉伦老宅
So you're saying that the McClaren House
有一个密室
has a hidden alcove?
这就解释了一切
It explains everything.
谋杀怎么会都发生在同一间屋子
How come the killings only happen in that one room?
凶手怎么可以随意出现又消失
How does the killer seemingly appear and disappear at will?
这些答案目前还有待查实
Answers that have, thus far, remained elusive.
说到这个  你的排查怎么样了
Speaking of which, how did your canvassing go?
一无所获
I came up empty.
完全没有证据显示马特·本顿
There's absolutely no evidence that Matt Benton
曾去过法威克
was ever at the Fairwyck.
也许他人已经回来的证据
Maybe the evidence of his return
就藏在那密室里
will be in that alcove.
值得一试
It's worth a shot.
我们明早去瞧瞧
We'll go first thing in the morning,
看看会有什么发现
see what we come up with.
你现在就想去
You want to go now?
当然了  除非你害怕
Well, unless, of course, you're afraid.
-才不  -不  我明白
- Yeah, right. - No, I get it.
那屋子闹鬼
I mean, it is a haunted house.
我不怕  卡塞尔
I'm not scared, Castle.
不不  你说得对
No, no, you're right.
你说得对  恶鬼已经尝过鲜血的甜美了
You're right. I mean, the demon has tasted fresh blood.
它的嗜血
Its--its thirst may not
是一个被害人所不能满足的
be slaked with just one victim.
好吧  行了
Okay, come on.
如果你不害怕
Listen, if-- if you're not scared,
-就说出来  -不要
- Just say it. - No.
拜托  你明明想说
Come on. You know you want to.
我不想说  卡塞尔
I don't want to say it, Castle.
就算为了我  求你
For me. Please.
我才不怕什么鬼魂
I ain't afraid a' no ghosts.
多谢
Thank you.
我不确定  卡塞尔  多年来这里发生了
I don't know, Castle, there have been a lot of murder investigations
多起谋杀案
in here over the years,
我想如果这里真有密室
And I think they would've found a secret room
应该早就有人发现了
if there actually was one.
如果它隐蔽得好  就不会
Not if it was hidden well enough.
如果我们真找到这间房  你会后悔的
You know, you're gonna regret it if we actually find this room.
为什么
Why is that?
因为那样你就得承认
Because then you're gonna have to admit
幕后黑手不是什么恶鬼
that there is no demon behind all of this.
只不过是藏在密室里
It's nothing more than
无聊年迈的变态杀手
a boring old psycho killer hiding in a room.
除非是个被恶鬼附身的变态杀手
Well, unless it's a psycho killer possessed by a demon.
你为何这么坚定地
Why are you so determined
要在其中找到超自然的存在
to find the supernatural in all this?
你为何这么坚定地不相信呢
Why are you so determined not to?
你知道吗  证据指向哪里
You know what? I am just following the evidence
我就会顺其追查
wherever it may lead,
而作为一名警察  我会考虑
And as a cop, I'm going to consider
这世上所有可能存在的解释
every possible worldly explanation.
要是没有呢
And what if there is none?
那我会考虑其他可能性
Well, then I'm open to the alternatives.
-你会相信妖魔鬼怪  -你知道吗
- You, skepticism maximum? - You know what?
就因为我不常把它挂在嘴边
Just because I don't talk about it nonstop
不代表我不相信它的存在
doesn't mean I don't believe in another plane.
我还亲身经历过呢
I've actually had my own experiences.
胡说  比如呢
Get out. Like what?
当我还是个小女孩的时候
When I was a little girl,
我父母在湖边租了个小木屋
My parents rented a cabin by a lake,
有天晚上  我要去洗手间
And one night, I had to go to the bathroom...
算了  你只会觉得我疯了
You know what? You're just gonna think I'm crazy.
不不不  继续说  告诉我吧
No, no, no. Go ahead. Tell me.
就在去的路上
and on the way there,
我听到一个声音在低语
I heard this... voice whispering...
叫着"凯特  凯特"
"Kate, Kate."
声音是从房东锁住的那件房间传出来的
it was coming from this room that the owners had locked up
房东告诉我父母  绝不要进那间房
and told my parents... never to go in it.
可那天晚上  门缝里发出奇怪的光
except that night, There's this weird glow underneath the door,
然后我又听到那个声音
and then I heard the voice again.
"凯特"
"Kate."
我走到门边
and so I walked up to the door
这时候  门却没有锁
And this time, it wasn't locked.
我扭开门把手  推开门  我看见了
and I turned the doorknob and I opened it up and then I saw it.
什么  你看见了什么
What was it? What did you see?
真好笑啊
Ah, ha ha. Very funny.
你唬住我了
Yes, you got me.
你认识我多久了  卡塞尔
How long have you known me, Castle?
我当然不相信有妖魔鬼怪
Of course I don't believe in ghosts.
那怎么回事
What was that?
太奇怪了
Well, that's odd.
不  可不仅仅是奇怪
No, that's more than just odd.
这与杰克·辛克莱被杀时
This is the same sequence of events
发生的事情一样
that preceeded Jack Sinclair's murder.
可杰克当时手里只有个电磁仪
Except Jack only had an E.M.F. Meter.
而我有枪和电筒
I've got a gun and a flashlight.
没电的电筒
With dead batteries.
我记得我刚换了新的电池
I could swear I just put in new ones.
我刚看到蜡烛边有些火柴
I know I saw some matches by one of these candles here.
-卡塞尔  有点大叔样行不  -抱歉
- Wow, Castle. Mature. - Right. Sorry.
找到了
Yeah. Here we go.
卡塞尔
Castle...
不是我吹的
That was not me.
好吧  也许是穿堂风
Okay. So maybe there's a draft here.
对吧
Right?
等等  我感觉它就在这儿
Wait. I think I feel it right here.
把我举起来
Give me a boost.
-好  准备好了吗  -好了
- Okay. Ready? - Yeah.
天啊  卡塞尔
Oh, god, Castle.
这轻而易举
Oh, yeah, this is easy.
卡塞尔  拜托  站稳了
Castle, come on. Just hold still.
天啊
Jeez.
那是录像里的声音
That's the noise on the tape
就在杰克·辛克莱被杀之前
Right before Jack Sinclair was killed.
好吧
Okay.
我要上去了  准备好了吗
I'm gonna go up. Ready?
抓住我的腿
Grab my legs.
卡塞尔  我说的是腿好吗
Castle, I said legs. Okay?
是腿啊
Oh, legs.
抱歉
Sorry.
可不如我可怜啊
Not as sorry as I was.
我整天都对着死人
I'm around dead people all day.
回到家里  我就想见到个活的
When I get home, I want a live one.
我累嘛
I was tired.
我不敢相信我们过了这么久才一起吃饭  宝贝
I can't believe we waited this long to do this, babe.
是啊  真是完美的一晚
Yeah, yeah. It really did turn out to be a perfect night.
我想要祝酒
I would like to propose a toast.
我知道这有点老套
I know that it's kind of corny,
但我就这样  我说了啊
But it's me so, well, there we go.
敬最好的朋友
Uh, to best friends,
从现在直到永远
now and forever.
干杯
Cheers.
还得敬未来的新婚夫妇
And to the future newlyweds.
-干杯  你真是太贴心了  -干杯
- Cheers. You are so thoughtful. - Cheers.
凯文说你们俩很般配  但
You know, Kevin said you guys made a great couple, but...
我没想到这么配
I had no idea.
那
So...
你俩打算何时结婚
When are you two getting married?
这样走很不舒服唉
Isn't this awkward?
别期望秘密通道
Yeah, well, secret passageways
是个特舒适宽敞的地方
aren't supposed to be the most convenient of places.
凶手撕裂杰克·辛克莱的喉咙时
The killer could have hung upside down from this bar
可能就倒挂在在横梁上
when he slit Jack Sinclair's throat.
这个情景可以支持你那
That would provide you with your
无恶鬼无阻碍的溅血理论
demon-free explanation of the undisturbed blood spatter.
卡塞尔  我很感激你的帮忙
Look, Castle, I appreciate the assist,
但是你不揉  我也行的
but I could do without the massage.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
你不是在帮我按摩脖子吗
Aren't you rubbing my neck?
没啊
No.
深呼吸  卡塞尔
Deep breaths, Castle.
只是老鼠罢了
It's just a rat.
那边有东西  走
There's something over there. Come on.
隐蔽的通道  密室
Hidden passageways, secret rooms?
我不明白了  卡塞尔
I don't know, Castle.
麦拉伦老宅的神秘之感
The mystery of the McClaren Mansion's
每分钟都在退却
looking less supernatural by the minute.
这是什么
What is this?
它是个磁场发生器
It's a magnetic field generator,
用它来破坏摄像机的图像
to knock out the video feed to the cameras.
有人精心设计
Boy, someone planned very carefully
要在杰克·辛克莱来这拍摄的当晚杀掉他
how to kill Jack Sinclair the night he was filming here.
它使得电路超负荷
It's taxing the power supply.
那就解释了杰克死前灯为什么闪个不停
That could explain the lights flickering just before Jack's death.
磁场也解释了为什么
You know, the magnetic field would also explain
我们看见录像带中的三脚架在晃动
that tripod moving that we saw in the video.
卡塞尔  看看这些痕迹
Castle, look at these marks.
这里曾经有张床
There was a bed here.
杰克出现前
Matt Benton could've been here
马特·本顿也许在这住过一段时间
for days before Jack even showed up.
自从梅兰妮·本顿死后
You know, this house has been largely unoccupied
这房子基本上空置着
since the Melanie Benton killing.
也许他们找不到马特·本顿
Maybe the reason they couldn't find Matt Benton
是因为他从未离开过
is because he never left.
他可能一直都住在这里
He could've been living here the whole time.
或许他现在就在这
And maybe he's here right now.
去开门
Open the door.
我的上帝啊   我的心脏
Oh, my god. My heart.
吓死我了
I was so scared.
怎么了
What?
不是吧
Really? Really?
这件外套人家不要了
I am throwing away this coat.
看  他袖口上绣有字母
Look, his cuffs are monogrammed.
"M.B."
看来你的推断是正确的
Looks like you were right, Castle.
马特·本顿从没离开麦拉伦老宅
Matt Benton never did leave the McClaren Mansion.
牙科档案证实
Dental records confirm it.
他就是马特·本顿
That's Matt Benton.
技术组需要更好的软件
Tech really needs better software.
死因呢
Cause of death?
现在还不能确定
Don't know yet,
但我认为肯定不是因为藏猫猫藏久了藏死的
but I'm guessing it wasn't the world's longest game of hide-and-seek.
他死了多久了
How long was he in there for?
还在等测试结果
Still waiting on the test results,
组织样本的初步报告显示
but the prelim reports on the tissue samples suggests
他死了将近二十年
he died about 20 years ago.
那么有可能
Okay, so then odds are
他和他妻子在同一时间被杀
he was killed at the same time his wife Melanie was.
凶手藏匿马特的尸体
So the killer hides Matt's body,
让人误以为马特是凶手
making it appear as though he fled,
杀妻后畏罪潜逃
framing Matt for his wife's murder,
让所有人都放弃寻找真凶
and throwing everyone off the trail of the real killer.
它奏效了   二十年来没人发现
And it worked, too, for 20 years.
直到杰克·辛克莱出现
Yeah, until Jack Sinclair showed up.
-测试结果出来通知我  -好的
- Let me know about the test results. - Okay.
四人晚餐吃的愉快吗
How'd that double date go?
我只是
I-I just...
还有件事
You guys... One thing.
如果马特二十年前就被杀了
If Matt was killed 20 years ago,
那他十五年前是如何寄那些明信片给彼得的
then how'd he send those postcards to Pete 15 years ago?
我想是时候好好查查彼得·本顿了
I think it's time we took a harder look at Pete Benton.
别问约会的事
Don't ask about the date.
我说了我很抱歉  好吗
Look, I said I'm sorry, okay?
我不是故意乌鸦嘴的
I didn't mean to jinx the dinner.
真是完美的一晚
"This really is the perfect night."
珍妮有点情不自禁
Jenny got a little caught up in the moment.
你俩什么时候结婚
"When are you two getting married"?
那是决不能问的问题
That's a question you do not ask.
好吧  其实
All right, you know, it's--
不完全是你们的错
it's not entirely you guys' fault.
你们俩后来大吵了一架吗
You guys have a big fight after?
大吵  没有
Big fight? No.
比大吵更厉害
Mega fight? Yes.
重点是  我们
The point is... we, um,
我们决定分开冷静下
we decided that we're gonna cool things off.
什么  你是说你们分手了
What, you mean split up?
是的  直到我们弄清楚彼此想要什么
Yeah. Just until we both figure out what we want.
哥们  我很抱歉
Man, I'm so sorry.
不管怎样
Anyway...
哥们  如果你需要我
Look, brother, if you need me for anything,
不管什么事我都挺你  怎么了
you know I'm always here to-- what?
也许不是重要发现  但
Well, maybe nothing, but...
这个灯泡
This lightbulb...
是新的
is brand-new.
你们在跟我开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
探长  这算得上是骚扰了
Detective, this is bordering on harassment.
我已经告诉了你关于我弟弟的一切
I told you everything I know about my brother.
你隐瞒了一些
Not everything.
你曾经订过婚  不是吗  本顿先生
You were engaged once, weren't you, Mr. Benton?
同梅兰妮·温德尔
To a Melanie Wendell.
后来梅兰妮悔婚
Until Melanie broke it off
转而嫁给了你弟弟
and married your brother instead.
我们没能走到最后
Things didn't work out for us.
我没期望梅兰妮会一直单身
I didn't expect Melanie to stay single forever.
但是你再没结过婚
But you never married,
因为你从未忘记过她  对吗
Because you never got over her, did you?
彼得  寄那些明信片的到底是谁
Who really sent those postcards, Pete?
是你自己寄的吗
Did you send 'em yourself?
你们在胡说什么啊
What the hell are you talking about?
我弟弟寄给我的
My brother sent me those postcards.
你我都知道那是不可能的
You and I both know that's not possible.
你弟弟已经死了二十年了
Your brother has been dead for 20 years.
什么
What?
我们在麦拉伦老宅发现了他的尸体
We found his remains in the McClaren house.
事情败露了
It's over.
你以为是我杀了自己弟弟
You think I killed my brother?
你以为是我杀了梅兰妮
You think I killed Melanie?
那晚你在哪  彼得
Where were you that night, Pete?
我会明明白白地告诉你那晚我在哪
I'll tell you exactly where I was.
我和我朋友玛丽共进晚餐
I went to dinner with my friend Marie--
73街  如爱餐馆
73, Cafe Jouer.
我们九点离开的
We were out by 9:00.
后来我们去杜兰酒吧喝酒
We stopped at Dorian's for a drink.
我点了杯七七 [鸡尾酒]
I had a 7 and 7.
为我们服务的是帕特克
Our server was Patrick.
那样的事情发生时
When something like that happens,
它会深深地刻在你脑海里
it's burned into your brain.
那晚你听到的每个细节
Every detail of what happened the night you heard.
我怎么忘也忘不掉
I couldn't forget it if I tried.
彼得  我们会去证实你的说辞
We're gonna have to verify your story, Pete.
这么说  我
So... My--
梅兰妮不是我弟弟杀死的
my brother didn't kill Melanie?
我们不认为是他干的
We don't think so.
我一直以为是他做的
I've always assumed that he did.
马特脾气暴躁
Matt had a terrible temper.
他坚信梅兰妮出轨了
He was convinced that Melanie was cheating on him.
她有吗
Was she?
如果她有我也不会感到震惊
Wouldn't surprise me if she was.
马特怀疑是与她共事的人
Matt thought it was somebody at work.
不是跟梅兰妮共事的人
It wasn't someone Melanie worked with.
我刚跟乔治·本纳谈过
I just tracked down George Banner,
二十年前梅兰妮在畅游旅行的上司
Melanie's manager at Fly-wide Travel from 20 years ago.
他说梅兰妮有两个同事
He said Melanie had two coworkers,
都是男的
both guys...
-已婚   -结婚也可以乱搞嘛
- Married... - Still?
同性婚姻
to each other.
畅游以前在市中心的高层写字楼
Well, Fly-wide was in a high-rise in midtown.
也许出轨的对象是楼里的其他人
So maybe it was someone else in the building.
我们去查查当年梅兰妮在那工作时
Let's get a list of all the tenants that were there
还有哪些人租了写字楼
when Melanie worked there.
我想没这个必要了
I'm not sure that's necessary.
还记得我从那个密室里拿的灯泡吗
Remember the lightbulb I took from that secret room?
-当然  -我去查了灯泡的序列号
- Yeah.  - Well, I traced the serial number.
那个灯泡是厂商直销给福勒物业
It belongs to a lot that was sold by the manufacturer
一批灯泡中的一个
directly to Fuller Estate Management.
-史蒂夫·福勒的公司吗  -正是麦拉伦老宅宅主
- As in Steve Fuller?  - Owner of the McClaren mansion.
那也就是说福勒知道那间密室的存在
That means that Fuller knew about that room
却没告诉我们
and didn't tell us.
而他故意隐瞒只有一个理由
There's only reason why he wouldn't tell us...
那就是他才是真正的凶手
because he's the killer.
也许马特·本顿猜得没错
Maybe Matt Benton was right about
梅兰妮的确有外遇
Melanie having an affair,
但是他却猜错了她的外遇对象
only wrong about who she was having the affair with.
-但是  -当事情败露后  他就杀了她
- But --  - And when things went bad, he killed her,
还有马特  然后把尸体藏在自己的房子里
killed Matt, and stashed his body in his own house
他知道没人找得到
where he knew no one would find it.
而且他还计划要毁尸灭迹
And he planned on destroying the evidence.
他在那几起谋杀案过后
He wanted to have the house torn down
还想拆掉房子
right after those murders,
-但房子却被列为地标  -慢
- but it was declared a landmark.  - Y --
于是他就利用密道来吓走租客
So he used that passageway to scare off
比如博伊尔一家  让鬼宅越传越邪
tenants like the Boyers, growing the mansion's legend
以至于没人再敢住进去了
so that no one would want to live there.
然后杰克·辛克莱又跑来四处打探
And then when Jack Sinclair came sniffing around,
他不得再开杀戒
he had to kill him, too.
说完了吧
You guys.
故事很精彩  但是检察官才不会买账呢
Great story. The D.A. will never buy it.
这不能直接证明他有罪
It's all circumstantial.
她说得没错
She's right.
可能是任何人安装的灯泡
Anyone could've put that bulb in there.
我们没有证据
We have no proof.
证据会有的
But we will.
我想我有办法让福勒先生
And I think I know just how to get Mr. Fuller
把心中的鬼给招出来
to give up the ghost.
-你觉得他会来吗  -不知道
- Think he'll show?  - I don't know.
-你跟他说了明天的事了吧  -说了  卡塞尔
- You told him about tomorrow, right?  - Yes, Castle.
他以为我们明天就要近密室一探究竟
He thinks we're going through that wall in the morning.
所以如果福勒就是凶手的话
So if Fuller's our guy,
他今晚就该来转移马特·本顿的尸体
he should be coming for Matt Benton's body tonight.
前提是他是真凶  备不住根本就不是他干的
If he's our guy. I mean, he might not be our guy.
说曹操曹操到
And yet, there he is.
当然啦  他也有可能是来修马桶的
Of course, he might just be here to fix a busted toilet.
需要帮忙吗  福勒
Need a hand with that, Fuller?
史密斯警探
Detective Smith?
贝克特探长
Detective Beckett.
一直以来
It was...you...
都是你  为什么
all this time. Why?
你知道吗  他一直对她施暴
You know, he was abusing her.
下手残忍
Terrible things.
我们没有一个月
I don't think a month went by,
不接到来自这里的报警电话的
we didn't get called up to this house.
我有一天下午过来  想看看她是否一切都好
And one day, I stopped by in the afternoon to check on her.
你是她的外遇对象
You were the affair.
那根本不是外遇
It wasn't an affair.
而是爱
It was love.
那你为什么要杀她
Then why'd you kill her?
我没想要杀她  但是
I didn't mean to. It just...
她想跟我分手
She wanted to call it off with me.
我无法接受
And I couldn't let that happen.
那马特·本顿呢
And Matt Benton?
他那样对待她  纯属是死有余辜
The way he treated her, he deserved what he got.
作为案件的主要负责人
And as the lead officer,
你知道你可以把调查方向引开
you knew you could steer the investigation off yourself
引到一个他们永远都找不到的人身上
and on to someone they'd never find.
然后你又寄来了那些明信片
And then you sent those postcards
让人们以为你的疑犯还活着
to keep your suspect alive.
我让大家以为他才是凶手
I had 'em think that he did it.
反正这一切本来也都是他的错
It was his fault anyway.
那杰克·辛克莱呢  你是怎么知道他来打探
What about Jack Sinclair? How'd you find out about him?
我答应过福勒  我总有一天要破了这个案子
I promised Fuller that I would solve this case one day.
我让他无论有任何进展都通知我
I asked him to keep me informed of any developments.
所以当杰克联系福勒提及犯罪现场时
So that when Jack contacted Fuller about the crime scene,
他给你打了电话
he called you.
当我们告诉福勒  我们准备
And when we told Fuller we were gonna
明天清查那个房间的时候
check out that room tomorrow,
他也打了电话给你
he called you then, too.
你们俩都很聪明
You're both very smart.
但是你们忘了一件事
But you're forgetting one thing.
这个房子闹鬼
This house is haunted.
谢谢你的枪  探长  真的很感谢
Thanks for the gun, detective. I really appreciate it.
我对辛克莱表示遗憾  真的
You know, I felt bad about Sinclair. I really did.
但那晚的事他知道的太多了
But he knew too much about that night,
连报上没登的也知道
stuff that wasn't in the papers.
所以他不得不死
So he had to go.
跪下
Get on your knees.
别担心  卡塞尔  他不会开枪的
Don't worry, Castle. He's not gonna shoot us.
那就与传说不符了
That won't fit the legend.
你还有什么有用信息要跟凶手讲吗
Any more helpful hints you'd care to pass along to our killer?
跪下
On your knees.
我不要  艾迪森
I don't think so, Addison.
你也知道  恶鬼只有在
Y-you see, the demon
神不知鬼不觉的情况下才杀人
only really kills when no one's looking.
但今晚  我们可是有观众
And tonight, we have an audience.
你招供他们都记录下来了
They recorded your full confession.
你有权利保持沉默
You have a right to remain silent.
人赃并获呀
So busted.
鬼赃并获
Ghost busted,
多亏了露露啊
thanks to Lulu.
为了他  这点小事不足挂齿
It's the least I could do for him, you know?
我是说杰克
For Jack.
这么说福勒根本不知道有密室
So Fuller had no idea about that room?
就像我们说的那样  灯泡可能是任何人
Well, like we said before, anyone could've grabbed
从宅子哪个房间取下来
the lightbulb from another part of the house
然后安进去的  看来就是史密斯了
and placed it there. I guess Smith did it.
他现在在检察官办公室写认罪书呢
He's in with the D.A. right now writing his confession.
我不明白的是
Yeah, well, what I don't get is,
如果他那么爱梅兰妮  为什么还要杀她呢
if he was so in love with Melanie, why would he kill her?
他说他是被恶鬼逼他做的
He said that a demon made him do it.
我敢说他只是为用精神失常辩护做铺垫罢了
Just laying the groundwork for his insanity plea, I'm sure.
也许吧
Perhaps.
拜托  卡塞尔  就算是你也得承认
Oh, come on, Castle, even you have to admit,
这一切  每个闹鬼的传说  每起凶案
everything -- every haunting, every death,
每件跟麦拉伦老宅闹鬼
everything even remotely connected
扯得上一丁点关系的事
to paranormal activity in the McClaren house
都能被密道解释
can be explained by that passageway.
这我可说不准
I don't know.
那咱们昨天晚上在客厅的时候呢
What about last night when we were in the living room?
门突然关上  灯和蜡烛熄灭的事呢
How about the door, the light, the candle?
线路老旧  到处漏风
Old wiring, drafty house.
也许不只是这样呢
Or maybe it was something more.
你好好想想  要不是你想知道
Think about it, if you hadn't gone looking for
吹灭蜡烛的风是从哪里吹进来的
the draft that blew out the candle
你也就不会发现密道
you would never have found the passageway
更不会发现马特·本顿的尸体
or Matt Benton's body.
就跟我这个不信鬼神的人直说吧
Spell it out for those of us that are paranormally impaired.
也许是有人想让我们发现密道
Maybe someone wanted us to find that passageway.
也许
Maybe...
杰克·辛克莱的鬼魂
Jack Sinclair's ghost
在帮我们侦破他自己的凶杀案
was helping solve his own murder.
好吧  这样好了
Okay, I'll tell you what.
只要你承认世界上没有恶鬼
I will admit to that possibility
-我就承认这种可能性  -成交
- if you admit there is no demon.  - Done.
有人看到
Did anyone see...
这还真是诡异
That was weird.
老爸
Hi, dad.
你还没睡呢
Hey, you're up late.
还跟阿什利视频捉迷藏呢
Playing skype-tag with Ashley?
没  我们终于聊上了
No. We finally connected.
是正如你所期待的那样
Ah. Was it everything you hoped for
而且更精彩吗
in a peer-to-peer video conference and more?
说实话
Honestly, it was...
还真不怎么样
blah.
他心不在焉  我也累得半死
I mean, he was preoccupied, and I was tired.
而且我们俩又有时差  烦死了
And this whole time-difference thing is a real drag.
异地恋不容易是人尽皆知的事实
Nobody said that long distance was easy.
是啊  但我也没想到会这么不容易呀
Yeah, but is it supposed to be this hard?
这么说吧
Well, I can tell you this...
任何一段
Any relationship
十分钟以上的恋情
that lasts longer than a breath mint
都会面临各式各样的挑战
is going to have challenges.
但是如果一段恋情最终结束了
But if a relationship doesn't work out,
通常都不是因为遇到了挑战
it's usually not because of the challenges.
而是因为
It's usually because
这段恋情一开始就不够牢固
the relationship wasn't strong enough to begin with.
好受点了吗
Does this help?
-没  -我想也是
- Not really.  - Yeah.
但是你的肩膀总会给我安慰
But this always does.
我可以向你保证
I can promise you this...
只要两个人有共同的信仰  坚定的信仰
if two people believe in something, really believe,
那么任何事  哪怕是最不可能的事
anything, even the impossible,
都会变成可能
is possible.
就连
Even...
食人僵尸也可能吗
flesh-eating zombies?
尤其是食人僵尸
Oh, especially flesh-eating zombies.
咱们上次看到哪了
Now where were we?
就在这
Yeah, right there.